astrobix.com 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy - Astrobix.com

We are committed to maintaing your privacy and security on the Internet, and our privacy policy discloses our information gathering and distribution practices. 

Any personal information that you provide to our Web site will stay safe, private, and secure. We will NOT resell your information to outside sources. We will NOT give to anyone free. 

We will not share your information with any third parties with the exception of verified secure ecommerce transaction providers for the purpose of payment collection only. 

INFORMATION THAT WE MAY COLLECT FROM OUR USERS 

We may collect the following information when you sign up for a service: 

* First name, last name, e-mail, address, phone number 

* For making of astrological reports we also collect birth details like birth time, place, etc. This information stays in our server and is not shared with anyone 

. 

* For processing transactions, we also collect either credit card information or bank information, depending on your form of payment. We do not store any credit card information after your transaction is complete. 

IP Address: 

When a user visits any Web site owned or operated by astrobix.com, we may collect the IP address that requested the display of our sites. This address is collected for several purposes. The first purpose is to exercise our ability to restrict access to the site by users who have violated our Terms of Service. A second purpose is to support our advertising partners, so that the partners will be able to accurately count the number of unique visitors to our sites who may have viewed a given advertisement. 

Any information you provide to us as part of your use of any astrobix.com Web site will be stored as entered. 

Cookies: 

The sole purpose of cookies is to enhance your online experience. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer by Web sites. Through your Web browser, cookies are only used by the Web site that wrote the cookie. Data stored in a cookie from astrobix.com is only accessible by the astrobix.com Web sites. We only store encrypted identity information in the cookies, and do not store any unencrypted info. 

USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION 

Your username, e-mail address, and password will be used to uniquely identify you as a user on any astrobix.com Web site. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions, reports or for identification. 

SECURITY OF COLLECTED INFORMATION 

All data that we collect is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network. Outside of our network, the only access to this data is that provided through our Web sites. Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our corporation, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to key personnel who maintain the database. All employees of astrobix.com, Inc. are legally bound by a nondisclosure agreement that prevents the disclosure of any corporate information to other parties. We have taken all reasonable precautions to safeguard the privacy of your data. 

E-MAIL/OPT-OUT 

When you create a customer account with astrobix.com, you will automatically be registered to receive one or more of our newsletters, even if you previously opted out of receiving newsletters. At any time, you may opt-out of receiving these newsletters by selecting the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any newsletter or by contacting us at the address indicated in the newsletter. astrobix.com treats each of its consumer offerings individually, so if you are receiving mailings from more than one area of our website, if you want to unsubscribe you must do so with respect to each such area individually. 

OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTED 

Your Web browser or client software that you use to access astrobix.com may transmit certain geographic information and information regarding the capabilities or features of your computer and/or software to us. We may catalog and preserver this information for our internal analysis and surveys. 

HOW INFORMATION IS USED 

The information you provide to astrobix.com will allow us to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, handle and/or route your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, free offers, prizes, or special events. astrobix.com may use personal information in combination with data from third parties for similar purposes as well. 

THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISING 

It is important that you understand that advertisers or Web sites that link to a astrobix.com site may collect personal information about you. The Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, other advertisers or Web sites. 

If, for any reason, you are concerned with the way that we may be using your personal information, you may request that we cease to use your information or you may file a complaint by contacting astrobix.com Privacy Policy Department, 76/2, 1st Floor, Garhi, East of Kailash, New Delhi-110065 

AGREEMENT WITH astrobix.com POLICIES 

By using any of the astrobix.com Web sites, products, or services, you signify your understanding and agreement to the Privacy Policy stated here, and to the Terms of Use. If you do not agree with our policies, please do not use any of the astrobix.com Web sites, products, or services.
